A Guide to the Papers of the Casey and Dudley Families, ca. 1923-1988
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Correspondence and Papers of the Dudley Family 1941-1986, n.d. (Box 19)
  - Charles Milo and Frances Dudley 1947-1985, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Nancy Whittier Dudley 1987 (Box 19)
  - Robert Whittier and Argentina (Copello) Dudley 1947-1986, 2 folders (Box 19)
- Photographs of the Casey and Dudley Families 1930s-1980s, n.d. (Box 20-21)
  - Photographs of Constance Dudley Casey 1930s-1950s (Box 20)
  - Photographs of Constance Dudley Casey and others 1960s-1970s (Box 20)
    [Lyndon Baines Johnson, Sen. Theodore Green, Arlene Francis, Lady Bird Johnson]
  - Photographs of Constance Dudley Casey and Joseph Edward Casey 1978 (Box 20)
  - Photographs of Constance Dudley Casey, Joseph Edward Casey, and others 1930s-1970s (Box 20)
    [Gen. David Dwight Eisenhower, Admiral Paul F. Foster, Col. James M. McHugh]
  - Photographs of Joseph Edward Casey 1930s-1940s, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Photographs of Casey children and grandchildren 1950s-1980s (Box 20)
  - Photographs of Casey and Dudley families 1950s-1960s, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Photographs of Herman Andrew Dudley and others 1940s-1960s (Box 20)
  - Photographs of Entertainers at Social Events, kept by Herman Andrew Dudley 1940s-1960s (Box 21)
    [Princess Grace of Monaco, Joan Fontaine, Lillian Gish, Dick Powell, June Allyson, Edgar Bergen, Irene Dunne, Janet Gaynor, Ann Miller, Barbara Rush, Walter Pidgeon, Bob Cummings, Erol Flynn, and others]
  - Photographs of Entertainers, some inscribed to Herman Andrew Dudley 1940s-1960s (Box 21)
    [Joan Bennett, Olivia de Havilland, Joan Fontaine, [Eva] Gabor, Lillian Gish, Van Johnson, and others]
  - Photographs and miscellaneous from Scrapbook kept by Herman Andrew Dudley 1940s-1960s (Box 21)
    [Shah Mohammad Reza Pahlavi and Queen Soraya of Iran photographs and miscellaneous snapshots]
- Camp Interlaken Memorabilia Scrapbook 1927, Bound Volumes (Box 21)
- Memorial Tribute n.d. (Box 21)
- Memorabilia of the Casey and Dudley Families ca. 1956-1964, Microfilm-Size Box (Box 22)
  Miscellaneous items including: passport (1956-1959) for Constance Dudley Casey; medal "Honored Guest Democratic National Convention 1964" [of Constance Dudley Casey]; Kennedy campaign button; Casey calling card plate; cardholder for Constance Casey; two baby bonnets; cigarette wrapper and matchbooks
  - Audio tapes of Watergate interviews and news reports recorded from television broadcasts by Constance Dudley Casey 1973, Microfilm-size box (Box 23)
  - Photographs of Constance Dudley Casey, Joseph Edward Casey, and others 1930s-1970s
    [Dwight David Eisenhower, Mamie Doud Eisenhower, and others]
  - Photographs of Entertainers, some inscribed to Herman Andrew Dudley 1940s-1960s
    [Joan Fontaine, Walter Lippmann, Rosalind Russell, Shah Pahlavi and Queen Soraya of Iran, Fernando Llamas, Tony Curtis, Barbara Stanwyck, Victor Borge, and others]
  - Miscellaneous items ca. 1927-1971
    including: Board of Education certificate, 1927, for Constance Marion Dudley; newspaper broadside, 1942, for election of Joseph E. Casey to the United States Senate; article, 1971, "Eisenhower Revisited..."
  - Photograph of Camp Quinibeck Juniors 1923